Welcome. Tonight, we unravel a chilling tale shrouded in mystery.
Our story unfolds in Saitama Prefecture, Japan.
Saitama, a province in the southeast, borders the vast Tokyo metropolis.
In the southeast of Saitama lies Misato, a city veiled in secrets.
Just 20 kilometers from Tokyo, Misato covers 30,000 square kilometers—a place where fate would take a dark turn.
Tonight’s case begins here, in the shadowed streets of Misato.
Our central figure: Junco, born January 18, 1971.
At the time of the incident, she was just 17—a high school student with a bright future.
She attended Rasio Minami High School, Saitama.
Junco was cheerful, sweet, and beloved by her peers.
Her father managed a canning factory, her mother a homemaker. She had an older brother and a younger brother.
The family struggled financially, her father bearing the burden alone.
To help, Junco decided to work after graduation.
She worked part-time in a household goods store and a plastics factory, supporting her family.
As graduation neared, she aced a company interview, ready to start a new chapter.
But fate had other plans. One night, on her way home from work, she encountered evil.
A demon crossed her path, and what followed would haunt all who heard the tale.
What happened that night? Let us turn back the clock to November 25, 1988.
[music]
It was a Friday, a seemingly ordinary day. After school, Junco went to her part-time job at the plastics factory.
At 8:20 PM, she finished work and set off for home.
The streets were dim, nearly deserted. Suddenly, a man on a motorcycle struck her, knocking her and her bicycle to the ground.
Before she could react, the man sped away.
A young man appeared, offering help. He warned her the attacker was from the underworld, and might return.
He offered to escort her home for safety. Dazed and frightened, Junco followed him.
But as they reached a secluded spot, the young man revealed his true nature: he too was part of a local gang.
His name was Hiroshi Minato, 18, a dropout. He attacked Junco, threatening her life if she did not comply with his demands.
Terrified, Junco agreed, hoping to survive the night.
Hiroshi took her to a nearby hotel, violating her trust and her body. But he did not let her go.
Instead, a darker plan emerged. He summoned three accomplices to a park.
The three—Shinji, Watanabe, and another—waited in a car. Together, they searched Junco’s bag, finding her diary and home address.
They threatened to kill her family if she tried to escape. Paralyzed by fear, Junco obeyed.
The group took her to Shinji’s house, a two-story home in Tokyo’s Aira district—a place that would become her prison.
[music]
Through phone calls, Junco’s parents suspected nothing. They believed she was staying with friends.
Two days later, the group grew bored and invited more friends to join their twisted games.
The noise drew Shinji’s father’s attention, but he was told Junco was just a girlfriend. The adults did not intervene.
Six men now tormented Junco. She endured unspeakable horrors, her spirit tested beyond imagination.
Even when Shinji’s mother discovered her, she did nothing. The abuse continued, day after day.
Winter’s chill seeped into the house. The gang forced Junco to dance naked, to stand on the balcony in the freezing cold, until she collapsed.
Her suffering grew. The group filmed their crimes, using the footage to further torment her.
When Junco’s father died in an accident, they mocked her grief.
One member considered freeing her, but was caught and threatened. The torture continued.
On the thirteenth day, Junco tried to escape, calling the police. But Hiroshi caught her, punished her with fire, and the others followed.
Her wounds festered, her body failing. Yet the adults in the house turned a blind eye, too afraid to act.
Junco could no longer walk, forced to crawl, to relieve herself where she lay. The gang’s cruelty knew no bounds.
They starved her, beat her, and forced her to eat filth. Her face became unrecognizable.
As her condition worsened, the group plotted her end. On the forty-first day, Hiroshi, angry from gambling losses, unleashed his rage upon her.
Junco’s consciousness faded. Her legs, rotting, could no longer move.
The group beat her for hours. The next morning, they found her dead.
They wrapped her body, placed it in a drum, and filled it with cement, hoping to erase all evidence.
They tried to dump the drum in Tokyo Bay, but police presence forced them to abandon it in a field.
Eighteen days later, Hiroshi and an accomplice were arrested for another crime. Under questioning, they confessed to Junco’s murder.
Police found the drum, Junco’s body inside, unrecognizable. Forensic evidence confirmed her identity.
The autopsy revealed the extent of her suffering—broken teeth, shattered bones, and more.
The gang was arrested and tried. The sentences, some argued, were too lenient for such a monstrous crime.
The case sparked national debate in Japan about juvenile crime and justice.
Some of the perpetrators reoffended after release, their names forever linked to darkness.
Junco’s tragedy remains one of the most haunting cases in Japanese criminal history.
May her story serve as a warning, and may justice never sleep.
Thank you for joining us on this journey into the shadows. Until next time, stay vigilant.